<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enterprise Plans on Sakuli E2E Testing and Monitoring</title>
    <link>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enterprise Plans on Sakuli E2E Testing and Monitoring</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sakuli.io/enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Forwarder</title>
      <link>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/forwarder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/forwarder/</guid>
      <description>End-2-End Application Testing and Monitoring: Your Perfect Combination Combining End-2-End testing with monitoring solutions proves to be optimal – because effective quality assurance looks over and beyond any given server: Automated End-2-End tests ensure that your web or rich client ecosystem will keep its promise. Ultimately though, the quality of your systems will be assessed by the users.
Monitor Critical Workflows Imagine testing your critical processes and workflows by simulating a real-world user, sending execution times, warnings and error messages (including screenshots of the system under test) to the monitoring system of your choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Configured Headless Container</title>
      <link>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/container/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/container/</guid>
      <description>Sakuli Container in a Nutshell Our pre-configured Docker container will run Sakuli in an isolated environment. This will ensure having the same setup and equal conditions for every test run. You don&amp;rsquo;t need an unlocked display for native UI interactions with the headless VNC image configured in every container. For debugging purposes, you will be able to watch your test execution live in a browser or a VNC client any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sakuli CLI Tools</title>
      <link>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/cli/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sakuli Core</title>
      <link>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/core/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/core/</guid>
      <description>All You Need UI Test Automation Sakuli combines web testing with testing on native applications. That’s all you need in order to perfectly simulate a real-world user. Design your tests, run them automatically and save a ton of time by dramatically reducing your manual testing.
Build Sustainable Tests Sakuli uses state of the art web-testing technologies like Selenium, wraps a lot of standard functionalities and use-cases into user-friendly packages, thereby solving most of the pain points encountered by test designers in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sakuli Hub</title>
      <link>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sakuli.io/enterprise/hub/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>